Finding Aid for the Anne Waldman Papers, 1945-2012
Anne Waldman Papers
- Naropa
  - Conferences and Panels, undated
    - General or unknown (2 folders), undated (Box 61)
    - Dharma Poetics Talk, transcripts (3 folders), 1982 (Box 61)
    - Personal Geography, transcripts of Robin Blaser, Robert Creeley and Michael Ondaatje, 1999 (Box 61)
    - Naropa-Prameni International Poetics Festival, master schedule, May 11-18, 2003 (Box 61)
    - Borders panel, 2004 (Box 61)
    - Socratic Rap, 1998, 2005, undated (Box 61)
  - Speeches and Interviews
    - Speeches (by Anne Waldman; includes other material: notes, schedules, etc.)
      - General (2 folders), 1977-2011, undated (Box 61)
      - A Declaration of Interdependence, David Cope et al., 1990 (Box 61)
    - Interviews
      - William Burroughs Interviewed, Rick Fields (interviewees also include Lewis MacAdams, Anne Waldman, and Allen Ginsberg), undated (Box 61)
      - Interview with Victor Hernandez Cruz, Eleni Sikelianos, 1991 (Box 61)
      - Open Secrets interview of Allen Ginsberg, transcript, 1974 (Box 61)
      - A Plea for Ginny, Allen Ginsberg, 1996 (Box 61)
      - Transcription of talk by Kobun Chino Sensei, ca. 1974 (Box 61)
      - Robert Duncan interview, 1978 (Box 61)
      - From a conversation with Kenneth Koch, January 11, 1980 (Box 61)
      - Surprise Each Other: The Art of Collaboration, interview with Lisa Birman, 1998-1999 (Box 61)
      - Ferlinghetti Rap, interview with Lawrence Ferlinghetti, 1998 (Box 61)
      - Interview with Anne Waldman for Ronna Johnson and Nancy Grace's book Girls Who Wore Black: Women Writing the Beat Generation, 2001-2002 (Box 61)
  - Publications
    - Campus Periodicals: student newsletters and bulletins (3 folders) 1972-2010, undated (Box 61)
    - Submissions, undated (Box 61)
    - Class Publications
      - Boulder Work: women-only apprentice class, August 1979 (Box 61)
      - The Drunken Book, Fall 1991 (Box 61)
      - Balls, Practice of Poetry I, Fall 1993 (Box 61)
      - Eleavenings: Plays on Word 1995 (Box 61)
      - At the Same [T]ime, 1996-1997 (Box 61)
      - Summer Writing Program
        - Astarte 1.1: Anne Waldman's personal copy, 1992 (Box 61)
        - ca. 14 lines, July 1992, July 1993 (Box 61)
        - Camp Kerouac, Summer 1986 (Box 61)
        - Manifesto, undated (Box 62)
        - Summer Langue, July 1993 (Box 62)
        - The Third Mind, 1994 (Box 62)
        - Something Worth Proposing, June 2000 (Box 62)
        - Radical Interventions, 2001 (Box 62)
        - Invention/Intervention: Activism as Performance, 2003 (Box 62)
        - Wake Up, 2004 (Box 62)
        - summer stock 2, 2006 (Box 62)
        - Summer Writing Magazine (6 folders), 1988, 1993-2012 (Box 62)
        - Radical Interventions 2001 (Box 62)
    - Other
      - Cassandra: A musical drama by Ed Sanders, performed July 24, 1993 (Box 62)
      - Aa day in the life of p. by kari edwards, 2001 (Box 62)
      - Reader for the Future [?], Carla Harryman, ed.[?], undated (Box 62)
      - Press Releases, 1977-1982, undated (Box 62)
      - Kavyayantra Press Reading Series programs 2009-2010 (Box 62)
  - Printed Material
    - Catalogs and Brochures
      - General Naropa (5 folders), 1976-1999 (Box 62)
      - General Naropa, 2000-2007 (Box 63)
      - Writing and Poetics Program (3 folders), undated (Box 63)
    - Posters, Flyers, and Programs
      - General (2 folders), 1973-2011, undated (Box 63)
      - Karmapa Black Crown Ceremony, 1974 (Box 63)
      - On the Road: the Jack Kerouac Conference, July 23, 1982-August 1, 1982 (Box 63)
    - Clippings
      - General, 1979-2011 (Box 63)
      - Naropa Poetry Wars by Tom Clark, June 1980 (Box 63)
      - Kerouac Conference, July 1982 (Box 63)
      - Allen Ginsberg Memorials, 1997-1998 (Box 63)
  - Other Teaching Activities
    - Arvon, 2003 (Box 63)
    - Naropa study abroad program, Bali, 1997-2003 (Box 63)
      Includes correspondence regarding program
    - Schule für Dichtung, Vienna, 1992-1999, 2007 (Box 63)
    - Stevens Institute of Technology, Hoboken, NJ
      - Instructor Evaluations, ca. 1982 (Box 63)
      - Cut Up Sonnets, Anne Waldman Writing Apprenticeship, 1980 (Box 63)
    - Omega Writing and Meditation Retreat, 1994 (Box 63)
    - New College: Gertrude Stein: A Reading, 1982 (Box 63)
    - New England College MFA Program in Poetry, 2005 (Box 63)
  - Personal
    (includes ephemera, personal correspondence)
    - Buddhism and health-related material, undated (Box 63)
    - Contracts, 1974-1990, 2002 (Box 63)
    - Correspondence (3 folders), 1980-2012, undated (Box 63)
    - Ephemera, 1975-1976, undated (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous business cards (Box 63)
    - Notes
      - Buddhist and astrology-related, manuscripts by others, 1973, undated (Box 63)
      - Work and performances, 1979, 1993, 1994, 2002, undated (Box 63)
      - "Anne Private," undated (Box 63)
- Other Activities
  The Other Activities series is comprised of 1 linear foot of material, and documents Waldman's activities outside of writing and publishing. The series includes material related to conferences and festivals that Waldman attended, material related to Bob Dylan's Rolling Thunder Revue Tour, various video and audio recording projects, attempts to sell Waldman's archive, and significant documentation of Waldman's involvement in social protest issues.
  - Activism
    - John Sinclair Freedom Rally, 1972 (Box 64)
    - Rocky Flats and nuclear energy and weapons protests, 1975-1986, undated (Box 64)
    - Oxfam America, 1986-1987 (Box 64)
    - Nicaraguan Cultural Alliance, 1987 (Box 64)
    - Council on Counterpoetics, 1989 (Box 64)
    - Boulder AIDS Project/BECAP ethics committee, 1994-1995 (Box 64)
    - Toward Freedom Foundation advisory board, 1994-1995 (Box 64)
    - The Not in Our Name Statement of Conscience presents: Poems Not Fit for the White House. Lincoln Center, program. February 17, 2003 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous social issues, 1969-1998, undated (Box 64)
  - Conferences and Festivals
    - International Symposium on Ethnopoetics, University Of Wisconsin, Milwaukee, 1975 (Box 64)
    - Cambridge Poetry Festival, 1977 (Box 64)
    - "The Second Sex: Thirty Years Later," conference, 1979 (Box 64)
    - Second International Festival of Poets, Rome, 1980 (Box 64)
    - Festival of India (Tour of Indian Poets), 1985 (Box 64)
    - River City Reunion, Lawrence, KS, 1987 (Box 64)
    - Poetry Days, Oslo, 1989 (Box 64)
    - Vancouver Art Gallery Readings (with Diane Di Prima), 1989 (Box 64)
    - Taos Poetry Circus and World Championship Poetry Bout, 1989-1991 (Box 64)
    - Dalai Lama visit, New Mexico, 1991 (Box 64)
    - The Beat Generation Conference, New York University, 1994 (Box 64)
    - The Writings of Jack Kerouac, New York University, 1995 (Box 64)
    - The Recovery of the Public World, Vancouver, 1995 (Box 64)
    - National Festival of Women's Writing (Female Eye Festival), London?, 1995 (Box 64)
    - Civitella Ranieri Foundation Fellowship, Italy, 2001 (Box 64)
    - Atlantic Center for the Arts, Artists-in-Residence, 2002 (Box 64)
    - Makeup on Empty Space: A Celebration of Anne Waldman, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor (2 folders), 2002 (Box 64)
    - Institut de cultura, Barcelona (inlcudes printouts of W.S. Rendra poems), May 2003 (Box 64)
    - Highway 61 Revisited: Dylan's Road from Minnesota to the World (2 folders), March 24-27, 2007 (Box 64)
      Includes notes and drafts for talk given at conference.
    - International Conference on the 20th Century American Poetry, Wuhan China, 2007 (Box 64)
    - New England College. Paradise is Stranged: Women of the New York School. Talk notes, 2007 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous conferences (3 folders), 1985-2011 (Box 65)
  - Recording Projects
    - Lannan Literary Video, 1990-1996 (Box 65)
    - Miscellaneous audio and video recordings, 1991, undated (Box 65)
  - Rolling Thunder Revue Tour with Bob Dylan, 1975 (Box 65)
  - Sale of archive (includes index of archive ca. 1975) (2 folders), 1976-1992 (Box 65)
  - "Street Works" performance, 1969 (Box 65)
  - 17 Ibarra. Anthology of writing from the Luminous Details workshop. Original work by Andrew Schelling and Joanne Kyger. Patzcuaro, Mexico, January 8-15, 2000 (Box 65)
  - Entanglement film script. Directed by Ed Bowes and written by Anne Waldman, 2007 (Box 65)
  - Time-Contradiction film script draft. Directed by Ed Bowes and Anne Waldman, 2010 (Box 65)
  - Follow the Sandpiper, script, undated (Box 65)
  - Add-Verse program for video and photography art installation inlcuding Anne Waldman, 2003-2005 (Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous, 2003, 2009 (Box 65)
- Personal
  The Personal series is a topical file consisting of 1.5 linear feet of material documenting Waldman's interest in Buddhism, her 1967 wedding to Lewis Warsh, a collection of memorabilia from Waldman's travels, and various playbills, museum programs and ticket stubs. Legal and financial records, as well as various and unidentified notes, jottings and telephone messages, are also included.
  - Address and phone number lists, undated (Box 65)
  - Buddhist related material
    - Buddhist "practice," undated (Box 65)
    - Vajradhatu Seminary, Alberta Canada, 1979-1980 (Box 65)
    - Miscellaneous (4 folders), 1979-2010, undated (Box 65)
  - Childbirth information, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Financial records
    - Bank statements, 1962-2000 (Box 65)
    - Bills and receipts, 1971-1988, 2003-2004, 2010, undated (Box 66)
    - Pay stubs, 1966-1987 (Box 66)
    - Food stamp and unemployment benefit applications, 1976-1979 (Box 66)
    - Taxes, 1975-1976, 1989-1990, 1992, 1999, 2009, 2011 (Box 66)
  - Legal records
    - 33 St. Mark's Place apartment lease, 1979 (Box 66)
    - 33 St. Mark's Place sublet suit, 1982, and 1984-85 (Box 66)
    - Summons regarding Rocky Flats Protest, 1978 (Box 66)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1987 (Box 66)
  - Memorabilia
    - Awards, 1979-2003, undated (Box 66)
      Includes National Endowment for the Arts, Literature Fellowship Recipient certificate, 1979
    - Boz Scaggs autograph, 1978 (Box 66)
    - Cards and greetings (2 folders) 1967-2008, undated (Box 66)
    - Clipping book, 1975-1976 (Box 66)
    - Playbill, museum programs, exhibit catalogs and invitations, scattered dates (4 folders) (Box 66)
    - Ticket stubs, 1977-1998, 2002, undated (Box 66)
    - Travel
      - France, 1963 (Box 66)
      - Greece and Egypt, 1963-1964 (Box 66)
      - South America, 1972, undated (Box 66)
      - India, 1973 (Box 66)
      - India and Nepal, 1978 (Box 66)
      - India, 1984-1985 (Box 66)
      - Miscellaneous travel (2 folders), scattered dates (Box 66)
    - Miscellaneous scattered pieces, 1974-2004, undated (Box 66)
  - Notes and jottings
    - Health related, undated (Box 66)
    - Telephone messages, ca. 1976 (Box 66)
    - Miscellaneous printouts undated (Box 66)
    - Miscellaneous (4 folders), undated (Box 67)
  - Wedding with Lewis Warsh, 1967 (Box 67)
  - Wedding with Ed Bowes schedule with script, August 2, 2003 (Box 67)
  - Friends Seminary (High School)
    - Coursework
      - Papers and reports, 1959-1962 (Box 67)
      - English quizzes, worksheets, and notes, 1960-1961, undated (Box 67)
      - History timelines, undated (Box 67)
      - Multiple subject notebook, 1958 (Box 67)
      - Multiple subject notebook, 1961-1962 (Box 67)
      - American history notebook, undated (Box 67)
      - Chemistry lab reports, 1960 (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous and unidentified notes and assignments, undated (Box 67)
    - Diploma and commencement material, 1962 (Box 67)
    - Newsletter, directory, and printed material (Box 67)
    - Writing
      - Poetry manuscripts, 1958-1960 (Box 67)
      - Quest Literary Magazine, 1960-1962 (Box 67)
      - The Stove: Friends Seminary literary magazine, Waldman contributor, 1958-1962 (Box 67)
      - The Oblivion: Friends Seminary newspaper, Waldman contributor and editor
        - Submissions and production material, 1961, undated (Box 67)
        - Page mock-ups, 1960-1961 (Box 67)
        - Proofs, undated (Box 67)
        - Published newspaper, 1955-1962 (Box 67)
    - Report Card, 1959 (Box 67)
    - Yearbook, 1959 (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified, 1959, undated (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 67)
- Early Years
  The Early Years series contains 2 linear feet of material documenting Waldman's school years, as well as her early interests in writing, acting and drama.
  - Pre-High School
    - Autograph book, P.S. 8, 1956 (Box 67)
    - Grace Church School diploma and commencement material, 1956 (Box 67)
    - Music recitals, 1955-1956 (Box 67)
    - Third grade composition book and vocabulary book, undated (Box 67)
    - Writing
      - "Our Life and Times": Family Newsletter, 1955 (Box 67)
      - "The Penguin News": childhood newsletter, undated (Box 67)
      - The Scribbler: school publication including Waldman writing, 1957 (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous, 1955-1958, undated (Box 67)
  - Bennington College
    - Clippings, 1965, undated (Box 68)
    - Commencement program, 1966 (Box 68)
    - Course descriptions and printed material, 1962-1966 (Box 68)
    - Event programs and announcements, 1963-1964, undated (Box 68)
    - Grade reports, 1962-1966 (Box 68)
    - Notes, notebooks, and handouts
      - Shakespeare, 1965 (Box 68)
      - Poetry and Theory, undated (Box 68)
      - Spoken English, undated (Box 68)
      - Introduction to French Literature, 1963 (Box 68)
      - Form and Milieu in Art, 1964 (Box 68)
      - Blues lyrics handout with notes, undated (Box 68)
    - Papers (2 folders), 1962-1966 (Box 68)
    - Professor comments and correspondence, 1966, undated (Box 68)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964, undated (Box 68)
  - Acting and Theater
    - Children's Theatre of Greenwich House, 1956-1962 (Box 68)
    - Senior Play, 1962 (Box 68)
    - American Shakespeare Festival, 1961-1963 (Box 68)
    - Philadelphia Theater for Children, 1963 (Box 68)
    - Bennington: various productions, 1964-1966 (Box 68)
    - "The Snipers," 1966 (Box 68)
    - Acting resumes, 1961-1966 (Box 68)
    - Tiara from childhood play, undated (Box 68)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified scripts, undated (Box 68)
  - Early and Unidentified Writings
    - Poetry, undated (Box 68)
    - Prose, undated (Box 68)
    - School papers and notes, undated (Box 68)
  - Correspondence
    - 1956-1960, undated (7 folders) (Box 68)
    - 1961-1962, undated (6 folders) (Box 69)
    - School notes and love poems (primarily to Anne Waldman), undated (Box 69)
- Family
  The Family series (approximately 4 linear feet and 1 oversize box) includes material related to Waldman's mother, father, brother, son and other relatives. The bulk of the series is comprised of material created by, or related to Waldman's mother, Frances Waldman.
  Although the majority of the material related to other family members is correspondence, manuscripts and other material can also be found in the series. Of special note are the manuscripts found with the Ambrose Bye material, which include some poems written with or transcribed by Anne Waldman.
  - Frances Waldman
    - Correspondence
      - Anne Waldman, outgoing (17 folders), 1958-1977 (Box 69)
      - Anne Waldman, outgoing (5 folders), 1978-1981, undated (Box 70)
      - Anne Waldman, outgoing, empty envelopes (2 folders), scattered dates (Box 70)
      - Anne Waldman, incoming (2 folders), 1955-1980, undated (Box 70)
      - Other correspondents (7 folders), 1924-1982, undated (Box 70)
    - Manuscripts and translations
      - "The Border Guards: Poems of the Greek Resistance," 1980 (Box 71)
      - "Christ in Rome" (2 folders) undated (Box 71)
      - "Mikos Theodorakis: The Broken Revolution" (2 folders), 1970, undated (Box 71)
      - Cesar Moro poems, undated (Box 71)
      - Miscellaneous (3 folders), 1966-1977, undated (Box 71)
    - Printed material, 1973 (Box 71)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Letters to Alice LeFevre (1 folder) 1910-1937 (Box 71)
      - Birth certificate and family bible information, 1942, undated (Box 71)
      - Christmas card list and envelopes, 1971 (Box 71)
      - Church of the Ascension, 1979-1981, undated (Box 71)
      - Condolence letters to Anne Waldman on death of Frances Waldman, 1982 (Box 71)
      - Greek material, 1972-1977, undated (Box 71)
      - Handmade cards from Anne Waldman, 1948, undated (Box 71)
      - New Year's Eve party list, 1980 (Box 71)
      - Play, "Joan of Arc: A Spiritual Entertainment," 1979 (Box 71)
      - Programs and invitations, 1966-1982 (Box 71)
      - Spanish class, undated (Box 71)
      - Fragments, notes and miscellaneous, scattered dates (Box 71)
  - John Waldman
    - Birth certificate: photocopy, 1907 (Box 71)
    - College and University Business article, 1952 (Box 71)
    - Pace College yearbook and printed material, scattered dates (Box 71)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 71)
    - Correspondence
      - Anne Waldman (outgoing) (5 folders), 1961-1994, undated (Box 72)
      - Anne Waldman (incoming) (3 folders), 1956-1992, undated (Box 72)
      - Frances Waldman, 1978, undated (Box 72)
      - Other correspondents, 1974-1993, undated (Box 72)
  - Carl Waldman
    - Correspondence with Anne Waldman (2 folders), 1964-2009, undated (Box 72)
    - Manuscripts, 1969, undated (Box 72)
    - School material, 1957-1963 (Box 72)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 72)
  - Ed Bowes
    - E-mail, 2003, 2008 (Box 72)
    - Interview by Anne Waldman, "Inside Consciousness, Conversation with Ed Bowes," first draft, undated (Box 72)
  - Ambrose Bye
    - Correspondence
      - Anne Waldman, 1993-1996, undated (Box 72)
      - Other correspondents, 1990-1993, undated (Box 72)
    - Manuscripts
      - A Day in the Life manuscripts and production material, undated (Box 72)
      - Miscellaneous manuscripts (some with Anne Waldman), 1982-1985, undated (Box 72)
      - School Papers, 1994, undated (Box 72)
    - Handmade cards for Anne Waldman, undated (Box 72)
    - Recording collaborations with Anne Waldman (Box 72)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 72)
  - Ted Waldman
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 72)
  - Ruth Le Fevre
    - Correspondence, 1964-1973, undated (Box 72)
    - Manuscripts, undated (Box 72)
    - Clippings, 1920s, 1930s (Box 72)
    - Scripts and plays, 1934-1939, undated (Box 72)
- Handmade Books
  The Handmade Books series (3 linear feet) is comprised of one-of-a-kind books made by Waldman and her friends. Often they were presented as gifts on special occasions. They are divided into three subseries: Anne Waldman, representing books by Waldman; Collaborations, representing collaborations between Waldman and others; and Others, that is, works by others.
  - Anne Waldman
    - A Novel: appropriation of a tiny paintbox, colophon reads "Gulf War, USA, Laugh NO Tears Press," undated (Box 73)
    - A Ritual Poem to Please Mothers, #2 of 2, 1994 (Box 73)
    - Baby's Pantoum, Christmas 1980 (Box 73)
    - Birthday Sestina, undated (Box 73)
    - Birthday Sonnet and Three Recent Poems, March 3, 1988 (Box 73)
    - Blue Iznic Tile Recompense, 1995 (Box 73)
    - Book of Squares and Rectangles, June 1969 (Box 73)
    - Change Fire City Nap: appropriation of a tourist map of Florence, Italy, May 1998 (Box 73)
    - Chen: appropriation, ca. 1995 (Box 73)
    - Clock, undated (Box 73)
    - Con Afecto Sincero [or South America ], 1972 (Box 73)
    - Dominoes: a little book of poems for Frances on her birthday, March 3, 1970 (Box 73)
    - 8 Poems, Christmas 1972 (Box 73)
    - Fast Speaking Woman: calligraphy edition hand-lettered and inked by Moira Collins, 1975 (Box 73)
    - Feminafesto, 2011 (Box 73)
    - I Like the Tinge Is Fresh, undated (Box 73)
    - I Wrote This in the Country, March 1973 (Box 73)
    - Image of a Saint, undated (Box 73)
    - Inside Dallas, November 19, 1971 (Box 73)
    - Interstices of (Female) Imagination, #2 of 50, signed, Erudite Fangs Press, Boulder, 1993 (Box 73)
    - Little Arrows, 1979 (Box 73)
    - Little Book for Hannah Weiner, 1997 (Box 73)
    - Little Clarier Book. Venice, Italia, February 25, 2008 (Box 73)
    - Maghreb: Au Lit/Holy: The Poems of Lesley Lefevre, undated (Box 73)
    - Makeshift (little poems), for Joe, pre-birthday 1971 (Box 73)
    - Marriage Poem for Mark and Kay [or Epithalamium ], May 1994 (Box 73)
    - May a Rain: appropriation, 1994 (Box 73)
    - Memoirs of an Elephant, May 14, 1970 (Box 73)
    - Men: appropriation, Malaysia Books, 1996 (Box 73)
    - Mother and Child, 1989, 1993 (Box 73)
    - New Day, June 11, 1968 (Box 73)
    - Occasion, 1980 (Box 73)
    - One in a Million, 1972 (Box 73)
    - Piccolo: appropriation, undated (Box 73)
    - Poems and Pictures, June 11, 1971 (Box 73)
    - Power Booth, undated (Box 73)
    - Red, 1990 (Box 73)
    - Reed Bye Birthday Schedule, 1979 (Box 73)
    - Seattle, November 20-21, 1972 (Box 73)
    - 6 Young Poems for Joe Brainard, 1971 (Box 73)
    - Sleep Shade, Erudite Fangs Press, in an edition of 2 copies, 1994 (Box 73)
    - Thirty One Leaves for Autumn, 1979 (Box 73)
    - 3 Poems with Sports, 1971 (Box 73)
    - To the Poet Turning 30, 1978 (Box 73)
    - Train Compositions for Joe Brainard, 1971 (Box 73)
    - Upadessa: Cycle of Desire, Rigpa Editions, 1994 (Box 73)
    - Was Any Exit A Very Large Gulf: a novel, undated (Box 73)
    - Untitled
      - "Announcing," March 11, 1969 (Box 73)
      - "for my beloved Reed Bye," February 1978-September 1978 (Box 73)
      - Birthday card, June 11, 1964 (Box 73)
      - "Radio and Television Coverage Welcomed": scrapbook/journal, undated (Box 73)
      - Notebook with glued-in images, undated (Box 73)
      - Telephone messages with beadwork cover, 1967 (Box 73)
  - Collaborations
    - Brainard, Joe
      - Real Life, 1967 (Box 74)
      - Untitled journals, undated (Box 74)
    - Bye, Ambrose. Galvanometer Alphabet Poem, 1994 (Box 74)
    - Riley, Naomi L. Plane Ride (Anne Waldman's goddaughter), August 19, 1978 (Box 74)
    - Schelling, Althea. The Silver and the Gold, Election Day Press, Boulder, 1996 (Box 74)
    - Schelling, Althea (photographer). Desdemona. Six Strokes of Sarasvati an edition of 7, 2007 (Box 74)
    - Schelling, Andrew. Epithalamium (attached note, "coll. w/Andrew Schelling for Julia Connor [and] Jim Anderson's Marriage"), April 2001 (Box 74)
    - Schelling, Andrew. Sources of Poetry, Zen Mountain Monastery, April 10, 1992-April 12, 1992 (Box 74)
    - Schneeman, (?). Dear Elizabeth. Words by Ed Bruce. Inscribed "for Ed December 07, 2008". (Box 74)
    - Author(s) unknown. Athens, ca. 1969 (Box 74)
    - Quaalude (facsimile). Inscribed "Happy Birthday and Love, Anne and Joe". Calais, Vermont, August 1973 (Box 74)
    - Various authors. Ambrose Bye's baby book: scrapbooks compiled with many contributions from Anne Waldman, Reed Bye, and friends; includes wedding photos of Anne and Reed (scanned facsimile), 1980-1981 (Box 74)
    - Collection 1967
      - Berrigan, Ted
        - The Adventures of Wonder Woman (Box 74)
        - The Michael Brownstein Story (Box 74)
      - Brownstein, Michael
        - A Hunter's Prayer (Box 74)
        - The Fucking Story (Box 74)
      - Dennis, Donna. [title: illustration of an empty speech balloon] (Box 74)
      - Fagin, Larry and Inglis, Joan. 3 Fam Sto (Box 74)
      - Padgett, Ron. New York Poets (Box 74)
      - Ricard, Rene
        - a comedy of errors (Box 74)
        - The Mother of Necessity (Box 74)
      - Schjeldahl, Peter. Killed (Box 74)
      - Waldman, Anne
        - Angel Hair Records 1967 (Box 74)
        - Book Rate (Box 74)
        - The Silver Box (Box 74)
        - The Ted Berrigan Story (Box 74)
      - Waldman, Anne and Berrigan, Ted. The Lew Warsh Story (Box 74)
      - Warsh, Lewis. 2 Poems (Box 74)
  - Others
    - Baraka, Amina and Baraka, Amiri. 5 Boptrees: hand-colored photocopy, 1992 (Box 74)
    - Berkson, Bill